Andrew Stewart

Atlanta, GA 423.255.8050 andrew@stewdioland.com stewdioland.com github.com/stewdiostash linkedin.com/in/andrewstewartwork/

Technical Skills

Apps

Adobe Creative Cloud, Sketch, Figma, Invision, Principle, Usertesting, Cinema 4d

Languages

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL

Projects

Bandwich

https://github.com/stewdiostash/ bandwich https://bandwich-app.herokuapp.com/

Play'tSafe

https://github.com/stewdiostash/ PlaytSafe https://stewdiostash.github.io/ PlaytSafe/

Education

Georgia Tech Full Stack Flex Bootcamp

Certificate Program Fall 2020

Judson College Bachelor of Arts in Visual Communications

Class of 2004

Summary

Product designer and developer with extensive experience collaborating with product, development and design systems teams to achieve complex goals. Focused on crafting user expriences that delight, inspire and empower. Dedicated to life-long learning and contributing to meaningful workplace culture.

Experience

Senior Product Designer, PGi, 2017-2020

- Led the design evolution of the GlobalMeet desktop app from a basic webconferencing tool to a multi-channel calling, chat and meetings experience, collaborating daily with multiple scrum teams and a design systems team
- Conducted extensive user testing and interviews
- Presented product research and proposals to large groups
- Founded "Code Club" lunch meet-up for PGi designers who code

Senior Designer, Macquarium, 2017

- Planned and designed web and mobile interfaces for Georgia Natural Gas,
 Mercedes-Benz Stadium, InfoTycoon
- Conducted regular work-in-progress presentations with clients

Senior Designer, Make & Build, 2016

- Planned and designed web and mobile interfaces for IBM, PrimeSport,
 Omnience
- Conducted regular work-in-progress presentations with clients

Marcom Designer, Kids2, 2012-2016

- Helped plan, design and launch Kids2 first responsive e-commerce website
- Participated in and managed multiple rebrand campaigns, including the Baby Einstein 2015 rebrand
- Art-directed and supervised numerous photo/video product shoots
- Planned and designed large environmental installations in US, Europe and Asia

Freelance Designer, 2008–2012

Partnered with small business, agencies and in-house teams on print, interactive, environmental and branding design projects

Associate Designer, Maycreate, 2007-2008

Assisted Chattanooga buisinesses with branding, advertising and interactive design services